{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"0.969/0.57",
			"answer":"0.969/0.57",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"28.6/2.2",
			"answer":"28.6/2.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8.06/0.0062",
			"answer":"8.06/0.0062",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.56/5.4",
			"answer":"7.56/5.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"55.8/62",
			"answer":"55.8/62",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"93.6/0.36",
			"answer":"93.6/0.36",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.85/5.7",
			"answer":"2.85/5.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7.26/0.66",
			"answer":"7.26/0.66",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"41.5/0.53",
			"answer":"41.5/0.53",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"16.8/2.8",
			"answer":"16.8/2.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}